<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pooya Mozzemi&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pooya Mozzemi&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Strategic Marketing Plan: Zalando</title>
      <link>/posts/a-strategic-marketing-plan-zalando/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-strategic-marketing-plan-zalando/</guid>
      <description>Section 1: Analysis 1.1 Context Zalando is Europe&amp;rsquo;s leading online fashion platform, selling all fashion products in all assortments from over 3000+ international and local brands as well as its own private brand products. It is currently operating in 17 european countries. It was established in 2008 in Berlin as a pioneering e-commerce shoe selling platform.
Zalando’s key markets are european countries. Zalando’s vision and strategy for the coming years is to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Design SW Products</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-design-sw-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-design-sw-products/</guid>
      <description>Identify functionality and use cases
This is the complete functionality of your SW system. This is what the system is built for. At this step all the functionalities and use cases of the system must be clarified. Normally, a SW system takes some inputs and then it performs some processing on it and then it returns some output or takes action as the result.
Example of static website generator
Identify characteristics of your product and system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Solve Chess Puzzles</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-solve-chess-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-solve-chess-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever seen a chess puzzle in a position you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do or where to start thinking about it? or you select a move and you think this was the best move and then see it was wrong? Here, I try to introduce a systematic way to analyze chess puzzles and solve them. This can be used as a framework so right after you see the position you know exactly where to start and check for alternative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Main Skills for Success</title>
      <link>/posts/the-main-skills-you-need-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-main-skills-you-need-for-success/</guid>
      <description>Hi, the main skills you need for success are here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
